peoplestrong.com 2019-05-15

# Privacy Policy | PeopleStrong

Data privacy is important to the PeopleStrong (PeopleStrong HR Services Pvt Ltd.) which includes PeopleStrong, and its affiliates. This Privacy Statement describes the information we collect about you as a visitor to [ **www.peoplestrong.com**  ](https://www.peoplestrong.com/)or other PeopleStrong websites that link to this Privacy Statement, how PeopleStrong will use the information provided, and with whom we may share the information. The Statement describes your choices and rights related to the information that is provided to or collected by PeopleStrong. ** **

 **The PeopleStrong Alt**

As part of the PeopleStrong Alt, customers/ end users may load data into the mobile application. PeopleStrong will not share or distribute any such Customer Data except as provided in the contractual agreement between PeopleStrong and the customer, or as may be required by law.

If you are a user of the PeopleStrong Alt, your use of PeopleStrong Alt is governed by your organization’s policies. Please direct your privacy questions or concerns to your employer or your organization’s PeopleStrong administrators.

### How PeopleStrong Alt Uses Information

 **Information Collection**

You may choose to provide us with your personal information, such as your name, email address, company information, street address, and telephone number.

In order to access some areas of PeopleStrong Alt, including PeopleStrong Community, you will need to have an account with a username and password. As part of your account, you may choose to provide us with additional information, such as a photo, social media profiles, or areas of expertise.

If you register to attend a PeopleStrong-sponsored event, we will require certain information including your name, email address, company, and in some instances, emergency contact. When registering for any event, we may also require you to provide billing information (such as billing name and address, and credit card number).

PeopleStrong Alt or PeopleStrong Alt Service providers may use website tracking technologies to observe your activities, interactions, preferences, transactional information, and other computer and connection information (such as an IP address) relating to your use of our websites and services. We may also use log files, cookies, and similar technologies to collect information about the pages you view, links you click, and other actions you take when accessing our websites, services, or emails.

When you choose to use a PeopleStrong Alt mobile app we will collect information from your device, such as your photos, contacts, or precise geolocation data, to enable some functions in accordance with your device settings. For more information about our mobile app, please see the section below on  **Mobile Applications**.

 **Use**

This section describes some of the ways in which PeopleStrong Alt uses the information we collect. Please note that there may be other uses, which we would describe to you when we collect the information.

PeopleStrong Alt uses the information we collect about you to provide to the PeopleStrong Alt websites, services, and support. For example, if you provide information to us in a “Contact Us” form, we will use your information to respond to the request.

PeopleStrong Alt uses your information for event planning and management, including registration, billing, and ways to connect with other event attendees, or to contact you further about relevant products and services. Any information you provide about emergency contacts or dietary preferences would be used for your safety and health purposes.

We use the contact information we collect from you and information about your activity on our websites to send you information that we believe may be of interest to you, such as product announcements, newsletters, educational materials, and details on upcoming events. We also use it to send administrative information, such as notices related to products, services, or policy changes.

We use the information we collect to understand how our websites and services are being used and to make improvements. For example, we may use the search queries entered into PeopleStrong Alt Community to improve search capabilities or performance. As another example, we may use questions posted or comments on PeopleStrong Alt Community to enrich the content or help guide future enhancements to our products and services.

Your information also may be used to personalize your experience on our websites. PeopleStrong Alt or our services providers use website tracking technologies to display products or features that are tailored to your interests and to present advertising on other sites.

We may use your information to diagnose website technical problems, as well as to prevent, detect, mitigate, and investigate potential security issues, as well as fraudulent or illegal activity.

In some instances, we may combine the information you have provided to us with other publicly available information. We may also purchase data from third parties and combine this with information we have already collected. We use this combined information to update, expand, and analyse our marketing leads; identify new customers; and create more tailored advertising.

If you participate in a PeopleStrong Alt-offered education or training course, your enrolment and attendance information will be recorded to track and potentially report your participation and completion. For example, completion of PeopleStrong Alt certifications by a services partner may be visible to PeopleStrong Alt and our customers, and completion of a training course may also be visible to the entity making the training available to you. This registration and tracking may be conducted by third parties on behalf of PeopleStrong Alt.

 **Disclosure**

PeopleStrong Alt may share information with PeopleStrong Alt affiliates, and third-party service providers or vendors contracted to provide services on our behalf. These third-party service providers or vendors may use information we provide to them only as instructed by PeopleStrong Alt.

PeopleStrong Alt may offer the following solely or jointly with third parties or partners: webinars, events, whitepaper downloads, or other services related to PeopleStrong Alt offerings or services. We may share your contact information and interests in these offerings or services with these approved third parties to communicate with you about PeopleStrong Alt.

When you attend an event (either sponsored by PeopleStrong Alt or one where PeopleStrong Alt is a participating vendor) and have your badge scanned, your information will be shared with PeopleStrong Alt, as well as with any partner or third party participating in that event, and potentially with the entity sponsoring your attendance at the event. For example, if your badge is scanned as you attend a session at a PeopleStrong Alt-sponsored conference, PeopleStrong Alt and any co-presenters will have access to that information to understand who was in attendance, and potentially follow up with you on relevant products or services. If you do not want your information shared with PeopleStrong Alt or partners in this manner, do not have your badge scanned. If your badged is scanned by a partner or a third party at an event, your information will be governed by that party’s privacy statement.

PeopleStrong Alt may disclose information if we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal processes; (b) protect and defend our rights or property; (c) enforce the website Terms and Conditions; and/or (d) act to protect the interests of our users or others.

If PeopleStrong Alt goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personal information may be among the assets transferred.

 **PeopleStrong Alt Forums**

You may post comments or questions on our websites; for example, on a blog, community site, or developer forum. Some of these forums allow you to provide your personal information and create a profile. Personal information you submit in these public areas can be read and collected by others who access them. You should only post personal information to online forums with the awareness that the information will be available to others in the forum (unless stated otherwise). Comments posted by individuals in an online forum reflect their own views and should not be considered to reflect the opinion of PeopleStrong Alt.

 **Do Not Track**

Without a common industry or legal standard for interpreting Do Not Track (DNT) signals, PeopleStrong Alt does not respond to browser DNT signals. We will continue to monitor further development of a DNT standard by the privacy community and industry.

### Additional PeopleStrong Alt Privacy Information ** **

 **The PeopleStrong Alt Cloud Platform**

The PeopleStrong Alt Cloud Platform allows partners and developers to build applications independent of PeopleStrong Alt. Before using these applications, please review the relevant privacy statement and terms of service.

 **Mobile Applications    
**

When you are using a PeopleStrong Alt mobile application, PeopleStrong Alt may obtain information from or access data stored on your device, to provide services related to the relevant mobile application. PeopleStrong Alt uses this information to deliver requested application services, to continue to improve our mobile applications, and to facilitate event participation, such as providing event schedules and the opportunity to connect with event attendees. For example, when you are using a PeopleStrong Alt mobile application, we may access your camera to allow you to upload photographs to the mobile service; access your calendar, social media, and contact information to allow you to interact with other event attendees; or access the geographic location of your device to enable you to identify nearby contacts. PeopleStrong Alt may also collect information from your usage of the mobile application to improve events and services, communicate with you about the event and relevant products and services, and for security purposes.

You may configure PeopleStrong Alt mobile applications, and this configuration will affect how information from your device is accessed and obtained in the mobile application.

 **Security**

PeopleStrong Alt employs reasonable and appropriate physical and logical security measures to protect personal information from loss, theft, misuse, unauthorized access, and unintentional disclosure, alteration, or destruction. You are responsible for maintaining the security of your password or other form of authentication involved in accessing password-protected or secured resources. In order to protect you and your information, PeopleStrong Alt may suspend your use of a website without notice, pending an investigation, if any security breach is suspected.

 **Data Retention**

We will retain your personal information only as long as needed to provide you with services or as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Data entered into the PeopleStrong Alt Service is retained in accordance with the agreement between the PeopleStrong Alt Customer and PeopleStrong Alt.

 **Changes to This Privacy Statement**

We reserve the right to change or update this Privacy Statement at any time. Changes to the Privacy Statement will be posted on this website and links to the Privacy Statement will indicate that the statement has been changed or updated. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Statement for any changes. For new users, changes or updates are effective upon posting. For existing users, changes or updates are effective 30 days after posting.

### Global Privacy Considerations

Personal information collected by PeopleStrong Alt may be stored and processed in the India or in any other country where PeopleStrong Alt or its affiliates, subsidiaries, or third-party service providers maintain facilities. When you provide personal information to PeopleStrong Alt, you consent to the processing and transfer of your information within the India and around the world. We follow applicable data protection laws when transferring personal information.

 **APEC Program Statement**

PeopleStrong Alt privacy practices, described in this Privacy Statement, comply with the Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation (“APEC”) Cross-Border Privacy Rules (“CBPR”) System. The APEC CBPR system provides a framework for organizations to ensure protection of personal information transferred among participating APEC economies.

### Contacting PeopleStrong Alt

 **Updating Your Choices**

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Statement, or if at any time after providing your personal information to PeopleStrong Alt you want to update, change, unsubscribe, or request removal or deletion of your information, or if you would like to assert any of the rights listed above, please direct your request to  **[privacy@peoplestrong.com](mailto:privacy@peoplestrong.com)**  or via postal mail at the contact information listed below. PeopleStrong Alt will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

PeopleStrong HR Services Pvt. Ltd.  
Attn.: Privacy  
A-10, Infocity- I,

Sector-34, Gurugram, Haryana

India-122001
